## **Pavel Kirilin**

Software Developer / Moscow, Russia / Email: kirilin.pav@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/pkirilin / GitHub: https://github.com/pkirilin / Portfolio: https://pkirilin.github.io

## Summary

Software developer with 4+ years of experience mainly on the .NET stack and knowledge of modern front-end technologies (React, Angular). For the last couple of years have been developing web applications and integration REST APIs based on cloud solutions (Microsoft Azure). Also developed small APIs and scripts using Node.js.

### **Skills**

C# | .NET 6 | ASP.NET Core | Entity Framework Core | MySQL | PostgreSQL | Docker HTML | CSS | JavaScript | TypeScript | React | Redux | Node.js | ExpressJS

# **Experience**

Dodo Brands / https://dodobrands.io / Moscow, Russia

An international franchise, which is developing food brands in over 16 countries around the world using IT.

## Developer (Jan 2021 - Present)

- Designed, documented, and developed 6 API endpoints used to integrate corporate services with third-party systems (accounting systems, bots, CRMs, SaaS services).
- Implemented the MVP of the applications marketplace service, which can be used by franchisee partners to add new functionality to the corporate information system and expand its capabilities.
- Created a dashboard that gathers the technical support team's performance metrics from 2 third-party SaaS services and identifies issues with the team's work, saving 2-3 days per week of collecting that data manually.
- Developed a bot that automates the technical support team's daily operations and increases the efficiency and the SLA of the team by 8% during the year.

#### Super Brands / Moscow, Russia

A distributor of more than 12 world brands of clothing, footwear, and accessories for over 15 retailers in Russia.

### **.NET developer** (Jul 2019 - Oct 2020)

- Increased the performance of sending orders to the internal accounting system by changing the existing integration from SOAP to REST.
- Adapted the functionality of importing and exporting products in Excel format for new data format to make search and navigation in export files easier.
- Provided technical support to the brand management team of 5-8 people and fixed several bugs based on their feedback.

### Quorum / Moscow, Russia

An integrator with 20 years of experience providing IT solutions for over 40 financial institutions in Russia.

#### .NET developer (Nov 2018 - Jun 2019)

• Developed and supported the application for automating banking loan pipeline

### Education

Bauman Moscow State Technical University / <a href="https://www.bmstu.ru">https://www.bmstu.ru</a> / Moscow, Russia BASc, Informatics and Computer Science (Sep 2014 - Jun 2018)
Robotics and Complex Automation, Computer-Aided Design and Engineering

#### Additional information

- Languages: Russian (native), English (upper-Intermediate)
- Citizenship: Russian Federation